What's the matter, young man? What are you doing here?
你怎么了  年轻人  你在这里干嘛呢
I'm looking for my little kitten.
我在找我的小猫咪
He's missing. Should I call the police?
他失踪了  我要报警吗
For your kitten? I think I can help. What does he look like?
为了你的小猫吗  我想我可以帮忙  他长什么样
Mmm... he has beautiful eyes. He's all white but black on the top of his head.
恩  他的眼睛很漂亮  他除了头顶是黑色的以外其余都是白色的
I guess you are feeling very sad.
我猜你肯定很伤心
Yes. My uncle gave the kitten to me only yesterday.
是的  我叔叔昨天才把他送给我
I hope he's not out there on the street. There are so many cars and buses there.
我希望他没有跑到街上去  那里可有很多的汽车和公交车
Perhaps he's just having fun in the garden.
也许他只是在公园里玩呢
Would you please look for him together with me?
你能帮我一起找吗
Sure. Let's go.
当然了  我们走